"Itazura na Kiss" The
Movie Production Committee
Tonan University
"The 1st year on campus"
"Spring"
Hey there, you beauties!
Yes?
Amazing!
Clubs in college really
recruit aggressively...
I wonder which Irie is gonna join?
You already live together.
And you wanna be in the same club, too?
Clingy Kotoko.
How rude!
We don't talk much at home anyway,
so I was hoping I could
join the same group...
Wait.
What's up?
Something wrong?
I got the feeling someone was watching us.
Here! Room 201.
This is our classroom.
The Literature Department!
Doesn't get more collegiate than that.
After being a loser in high school,
I can finally start over!
This place is an oasis!
Excuse me? May I sit here?
Wait, aren't you Mayu?
who graduated from Tonan last year?
Kotoko! Long time no see.
It really has been so long!
Good to see you again.
Oh, you look like the
model of a college girl!
I didn't recognize you at first.
But，
why are you here?
I actually failed last year.
So I'm starting over from scratch.
Nice to see you all again.
Same here.
Hello, Jinko. It’s been a long time.
Getting to take the escalator is great.
Yeah, really. It's fantastic.
Right, talk to you later.
Sure.
See you.
Something about this class...
Is giving me intense class F vibes.
Congratulations on getting accepted!
Welcome to Liberal Arts,
Department of Japanese Literature.
Listen!
If you can't make the grade, you will be failed!
Especially here,
the department of Japanese
Literature, every year,
has a lot of repeaters!
Don't let them label us
"The university's class F" again!
I thought I finally got rid of
the stink of class F...
Jinko, calm down.
I guess we'll never get out from
the shadow of class F after all.
You're right...
No matter where we go,
we're always gonna be Fs.
Work, marriage, posthumous title...
It'll even be on our tombstones!
Posthumous title?'
On our tombstones...?
Come on Jinko,
maybe getting something sweet
at the cafeteria will cheer you up.
Let's go!
Oh, Kotoko.
Did anything new happen
with Irie over spring break?
You've been living together
for nearly a year, right?
Yeah.
But, nothing happened...
during the spring holiday.
Really?
As usual.
Wait, the way you said that...
So something happened before or after?
Just say it.
Well,
on the day of our graduation,
he kissed me.
A kiss?!
Itazura na Kiss the Movie 2: Campus Chapter
The Science and
Engineering Department.
Let's get in there!
Wait, why?
Isn't it obvious?
We're gonna peek in on your darling.
What are you doing?
Kotoko wanted to see you!
You need something?
Actually, well...
Since it's such a pleasant day,
I was wondering what the desks
were like in the science department...
Just kinda curious...
Irie, is this your girlfriend?
Don't be ridiculous.
That's ridiculous?
Yeah, that makes sense.
I mean, you and her...
What's that chuckle mean?
Irie, let's drop by the cafe
and get something to drink.
No. Bye.
Puffer House
A toast to to Naoki and Kotoko,
who are now officially college students!
Cheers!
Congratulations.
Thanks.
Wow, amazing!
Time to eat!
Tasty!
Dear me!
Since Kotoko grew up
eating Ai's delicious cooking,
I bet she's a good cook, too!
Nah! On the contrary, she's
totally clueless in the kitchen.
It's actually got me worried if
she's gonna be able to get married.
Oh, don't worry.
Kotoko will marry into our family.
She will?
I mean that Naoki will marry Kotoko.
If Kotoko got
married to someone else,
Mr. Aihara would be all alone.
So she marries into our family,
Mr. Aihara can keep living with us,
and we'll all be one big happy family!
In that case, Ai and I would be relatives, then?
I agree then.
I don't!
I don't want a stupid older sister!
Right, Naoki?
Seriously. I absolutely refuse.
Well, I don't want that, either!
Huh, really?
After that passionate letter you sent?
Will you please accept this letter?
No thanks.
"Dear Mr. Naoki Irie,"
"I am Kotoko Aihara, a senior in class F."
"Your speech at the freshmen entrance
ceremony was so smart and cool, "
"that, for the past two years,
I've been in—"
You read it?
You're the worst!
You wrote it for me, didn't you?
You didn't have to memorize it!
I can't help memorizing the things I read.
Hey...
Does that mean, Kotoko,
that you liked Naoki all this time?
Uh... not exactly...
Just admit it.
I did write a love letter to him.
Wait...
You like Naoki?
Well, it looks like my plan
wasn't just a dream, after all!
Hold up a sec!
I’ve been listening to you guys,
and it sounds like you're
just saying whatever!
What're you doing here, Kin?
Oh, shoot, right!
It's nice to meet you, Irie family!
Kotoko and I were classmates at Tonan High School.
The name's Kinnosuke Ikezawa.
Another dummy.
Dad, why is Kin here?
I mean, the kid was pestering me
every day to let him work here...
I'm gonna learn everything I can.
Irie!
Hey, Irie...
About that girl from yesterday...
You mean Yuko Matsumoto?
She's a classmate in the Science
and Engineering Department.
Jealous?
No!
Well, she is gorgeous.
And apparently 5th ranked
on the national mock exam.
A very smart girl.
Not like someone I know.
Hey!
Explain these servings.
You got a problem with my totally fair
and equal portions, mister genius?
Kin! What're you doing here?
I worked at Puffer House at night
and in the cafeteria in the day.
Gonna work hard, save up,
so you can marry me whenever, Kotoko!
Kin...
Shocked speechless, huh, mister genius?
Yeah. It's pretty admirable.
Not sure about a man dedicating
his life to one girl, though.
Because I could never do that.
I hope it works out for you.
Say what?!
Sorry, can I get some more of this?
Hey, Irie.
Irie...
Long time no see.
Sudo...
I missed you so much, dude.
Come and sit here.
Irie, Irie, Irie.
You're gonna be
joining our club, right?
I wasn't really...
I taught you so much in high school.
Come on, please!
You only need to come to
practice when you feel like it.
With you in, we'll grab a
bunch of new female recruits...
Nah, I mean, we need someone with your skills.
I'll be waiting at the club
room after lunch, okay?
Kotoko... you crafty girl.
I knew you still wanted to
be in the same club as Irie.
I never said...
...That I didn't want to!
Okay.
I want to join you.
Wait... is Irie an anime fan?
Welcome!
I'm Aoki with the anime club.
We're honored to have a girl join us!
I love “Cutie Angel Mako!”
What do you like?
Ah... Er... Actually,
Where is the guy who just came in?
He came in and immediately
climbed out of the window
Idiot.
I've been tricked!
I've got the wrong room! Excuse me!
Tennis Club Training Room
The tennis club, huh?
You wanna join the tennis club, too?
Please!
Right here.
You didn't think this through, did you?
It's not like I joined because you did...
Have you ever played tennis?
Never. But they're gonna teach us, right?
You realize the difference
between clubs and circles, right?
What difference?
Welcome, new members.
I'm Hayashi, captain of the tennis club.
And I'm assistant captain, Sudo.
Tonan University's tennis
club has a lot of history
winning the Kanto championship last year,
and coming in third at the nationals.
And this year, we have
talented new members,
namely Naoki Irie, who won the
Kanto tournament's high school division.
Along with the girl's runner up, Yuko Matsumoto.
Listen up!
We're fighting for the national
champion this year.
That means you're going to work
yourselves ragged, every day.
Brace yourself. And no one
will be allowed to drop out.
I'm home.
Oh, welcome back, Kotoko.
You're kind of late, today.
Yes.
Oh.
Is that a tennis racket?
Yes, I joined the tennis club.
Oh my, Kotoko playing tennis?
I played when I was a student, too.
I actually taught Naoki how to play!
Really?
Could you teach me, then?
Of course!
Naoki and Kotoko, playing mixed doubles!
I love the thought of it!
Newcomers, line up!
Right!
To all of you new members...
We're going to have a basic test
to see where you're at, today.
A test?
What should I to do?
Sudo will be playing against you.
Glad to have you!
Everyone has two chances.
Sudo seems nice. I probably
don't have anything to worry about.
Ignorance really is bliss.
You'll be up first, Hijiri.
Yes, sir.
Okay, let's do this.
Ready when you are!
Hey, punk!
You got eyes or not?!
He ran away!
Spineless!
They call him "Sudo the Demon."
With tennis racket in his hands,
Sudo's whole personality changes.
Next, Matsumoto.
Coming.
Ready when you are.
You're pretty damn good.
Alright, done!
You returned my serve. Not bad.
Next, Irie.
Right.
You're finally gonna bow before me.
Let's take it nice and easy.
There's no way in hell that's happening!
Oh, now you've done it!
Sudo's taking this really hard.
I feel sorry for whoever's up next.
Yeah...
Next, Aihara.
Get your butt on the court already!
Okay!
Quit running! Get over here!
You numbskull!
I can do this. Okay... just
gotta focus on the ball.
You're joining a
snowboarding circle, Satomi?
Yeah.
And all they do is party,
when there's no snow.
Jinko, how about you?
I'm going for the light music club.
Lots of hot older guys with long hair!
You guys have impure motives.
Who followed Irie to the tennis club
when she's never touched the racket?
You're the one with the least pure motive!
My sweet honey, Kotoko!
Hey Kotoko, your number two is here.
Kotoko, got a message from your dad.
What’s the matter?
He wants to talk with you.
So he wants you to drop by Puffer House tonight.
What about?
Move out? I don’t want to!
We've been imposing on
the Iries for almost a year.
I don't intend on doing it forever.
But... I...
I know.
About you and Naoki.
The thing is,
Naoki's not interested
in you like that, right?
And seeing you like this...
It's frustrating for me.
I found a good house that's close to the restaurant.
Come on, Kotoko.
Let's get back to being on our own. Okay?
Come in.
Well... we're about to leave.
Yeah?
Will you miss me?
Feels like my life is finally
getting back to normal.
I see...
Sorry for all the trouble I've caused.
Right.
Alright, we should get going.
Let's do it!
What do you think? Pretty nice house, right?
Just the two of us, huh?
Come on, let's head in.
Mom, I'm hungry.
Is it time to eat?
Wow, it's already late.
I'm just not feeling it today...
Sorry, order some delivery.
I'm going to bed early tonight.
Yuki, you've got your old room back.
No need to stay in here.
Force of habit, I guess.
Just keep heading this way.
Oh, Dad mentioned...
Since Mom's feeling so worn out,
that the rest of us will have
to split the housework.
Got it.
Kotoko...
Hey, Dad. It's kinda quiet in the house now, huh?
Yeah, it is.
A friend of mine...
He's got a puppy that needs a home.
Can we adopt it?
Only if you can take care of it yourself.
Really?
Great! Thank you!
I can’t wait to see it!
This is gonna be great!
Here.
Pass me the salt.
Kotoko, salt.
OK.
You still not awake?
Hey!
Hey, you're stepping on a ball.
As a tennis player...
Irie!
You're on ball duty every day.
It's almost impressive.
Hey, Irie.
You here for a game with me?
I'd hate to embarass you, again.
Then when we head to Nagasaki for our summer training camp...
We'll play then. Got it?
Sure.
I didn’t get it.
Why?
They were out of stock.
Is that even possible?
It was unbelievable.
Huh...
Mrs. Irie.
Oh, how'd you recognize me?
Uh, it was pretty obvious, to be honest.
Listen...
Is Kotoko all right?
She's been pretty out of it, lately.
Kotoko...
I am so sorry.
But, y'know,
I honestly thought those
two would end up together.
Me too.
I mean, considering that, on graduation...
Y'know?
What happened?
Tell me!
They kissed.
I...
Have made a decision.
“Summer"
To our newer members,
this is where our training camp will be held in Nagasaki.
Starting today, you're all
going to undergo intense training.
This is our schedule.
Sounds hard.
This is for Aihara.
The smaller one, here.
You'll be handling the food!
For the whole club?
Yep. Simple enough, right?
Sudo.
When is our match going to be?
Right here, on the last day.
Matsumoto and I will be a doubles team,
against you and Aihara.
Got it?
You're joking—
Now, Aihara, could you
get cracking on today's dinner?
You don't want to let her practice, do you?
Don't be silly!
She'll be stretching and
running in the morning.
Swing practice and ab work in the afternoon.
That ought to be plenty
of training, for Aihara.
I understand.
Listen.
We practice whenever there's time.
Okay?
That's a lot of veggies...
And a big old pot.
What do I do?
For now,
I'll just have to get started.
Hey, is dinner still not ready?
We're not gonna have time to train.
Irie...!
Thank goodness.
Help me, please.
I recall something like
this happening before.
Oh, wait!
I can't practice with you
until the food's ready!
So...
Thank you for the food!
Delicious!
Nicely done, Aihara!
Good stuff!
Aihara!
Aihara! Aihara! Aihara!
Aihara...
Time for practice.
Okay...
Get back here.
Okay.
Get in a stance.
And hit it.
Get back into position, fast.
Okay.
And hit, fast.
Right.
Don't dodge. Focus on the ball.
Okay.
Poor Aihara.
Irie doesn’t need to be so strict.
You're saying that?
Stop avoiding the ball.
1, 2, 1, 2!
1, 2—
Irie... so cool!
Kotoko,
you've been doing a good job
with your intensive training.
I’ll give you a kiss as a reward.
Irie!
Irie...
You keep leaving practice in the evening.
Granted, I know I said you were a special case...
But tomorrow's the last day of the training camp.
Would you mind coaching some our promising newbies?
He can't!
Why not, Aihara?
Er, no reason...
So...
Is that OK, Irie?
I don't mind.
Are you sure?
Of course!
Counting on you.
Later.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
That's... burnt.
What is this?
Hey, freshman.
You try it, first.
Oh, okay.
It's awful!
What's going on here, Aihara?
Sorry.
All that other cooking... wasn't me.
Who made that then?
Who was missing from evening practice...?
Wait, Irie?!
This is going to be annoying.
Let's head out. I need to talk to you.
Yeah, alright.
I've been interested in you all
through middle and high school, Irie.
I actually planned on getting in Tokyo U,
since that's where you were headed.
And then, during the center exam...
I ended up next to you, by coincedence.
Thank you for what you did.
You remember I loaned you that pencil?
Of course.
I'm glad.
But then you ended up going to
Tonan University instead.
So I had to hurry to get in.
Hey.
Don’t you think we're a perfect couple?
Maybe.
But my test...
Ah, nothing.
What kind of girl do you like?
Good question...
She should be pretty, glamorous
and good at cooking. A woman of talent.
So, the opposite of you, Aihara.
I love intelligent men.
Matsumoto likes Irie?
What do you think about me?
Irie...
I...
But so do I!
Irie! It's not what you think!
Matsumoto, this is a misunderstanding.
Sorry to interrupt you.
But it's time for practice.
You wanna practice too?
I don't think so.
Let's see just how much Aihara has improved, huh?
Three set match, begin.
Here I come.
Out.
Score, 15-0.
She returned it?
That had to be a fluke.
Their swings...
Are slower than Irie's!
Here it comes, Aihara!
Out. 30-0.
Out. 40-0.
Aihara was able to hit my lightning fast serve?
There's no way I can stand that!
Chew on this one!
Backhand, Kotoko!
Right!
50-0.
Nicely done. We took the first set.
That's great!
Ow!
You twisted it...
Does it hurt here?
Ow!
I think you're done.
Sudo, we forfeit.
We do?
You can't play on this leg.
Let's head to the nurse's office.
I'm sorry.
We lost the game because of me.
I didn't expect to win in the first place.
Why make me train then?
I don’t know.
God, if I were to say I love Irie more than ever...
Would you be upset with me?
How much further to your house?
This is why I wanted to take a taxi.
But that'd be a waste.
You're heavy.
This is it!
My new house.
Well, tell your dad I said hi.
Okay.
Oh, excuse me!
Who are you?
Who am I? This is my house.
Uh, no, I live here.
No Aihara on the doorplate.
Ishikawa
What's going on here?
Where is my dad?
How could I know about your dad?
Weird kid...
Let's head to my house,
and then you can find yours.
Okay.
What the...?
Huh?
You came back together after all.
What kind of scheme is this?
We're renovating the second floor! Take a look.
This is Kotoko’s room!
And in the future, it'll be the
bedroom you share!
Share with who?
Why, you and Kotoko, of course!
The Aihara and Irie families
are back under one roof!
Cheers.
Cheers!
Kotoko,
I bet you're glad to be back, huh?
Dad, you could've talked to me about this.
What do you want? Seeing you so sad
after we moved out was starting to bum me out.
And Mama was completely
out of sorts from losing you, Kotoko!
But, I'm full of energy now!
Dog!
Why?!
You okay?
Yuki adopted him.
His name's Chibi!
So, you don't like dogs?
No! I love them, in fact!
Come on, let’s get this partys tarted!
Yeah!
Cheers.
Chibi!
Miss Aihara.
Any progress between you and
Sudo over summer vacation?
Progress for what?
Aren't you and him an item?
That summer night,
you were holding each other.
You make a great couple.
You've got it wrong!
Dammit Aihara!
Quit slacking off!
But Matsumoto just...
No excuses.
50 more sit-ups as punishment! Bang!
Aihara,
can I discuss something with you?
What now?
Look.
You like Irie.
But Matsumoto also likes Irie.
And I happen to like Matsumoto.
Yes.
So, shall we cooperate with each other?
Great idea!
Oh, Irie!
Say...
I was thinking of getting a different racket.
Would you go shopping with
me and help find a new one?
Alright.
Really? Wonderful!
So, how do you feel about meeting up
at Kichijoji this coming Sunday?
Sure. How does 1PM sound?
Great.
Alright. We're going on a date this Sunday too.
No way!
Hey stupid!
We're gonna be following them.
You in, or what?
I'm in!
Good!
Matsumoto.
Irie.
I like your outfit.
I'm glad. Thank you.
Let's move.
Yes.
How about this one?
This is cute!
Today's the last day of our sale.
Will you be picking it up?
Here you are.
One second please.
Here you are, it's all set.
Okay. Thank you.
Thank you.
Let's move, Aihara.
She's gone? Hey!
No bag necessary! Move it, Aihara!
But...
They're already gone! Get a move on!
Okay, okay, okay!
Ouch!
That was a nice shop. Thanks for taking me.
Sure.
You were a great advisor.
The racket should be—
Careful.
Thank you.
Sudo,
I think I'm gonna go home.
Huh? Why now?
I don't know if I can stand
seeing them like this much longer.
Excuse me.
Hey!
Boss, are you okay?
Keep your damn eyes open!
Sorry!
How're you gonna make this up?
Oh, your shirt's all wet...
You're gonna pay for this, right?
Yes, of course!
That's 100,000 yen.
A-a hundred thousand?!
1,500 is enough.
Say what? Who's this guy?
Who the hell are you?
Irie...
It's a cheap shirt,
so 1,500 should cover the cleaning costs.
You trying to start something, punk?!
Sudo, if you could take it from here.
Maybe we take what we're
owed out of your scrawny butt instead.
What the hell, dude? You really pissed them off!
Matsumoto, I need your racket.
Sudo can see you home.
You gonna pay or not?
Let's go.
Get back here!
My racket...
Come get some.
I'm running with Irie...
It seems like a dream.
We should be far enough, now.
Irie, did you know we were following you?
Of course.
Sorry.
Let’s take a walk.
OK.
God, I am so happy right now.
I might've used up a whole lifetime's
worth of happiness today!
That's how glad I am!
Did you know...?
Know what?
Supposedly the boats here are
famous for causing couples to break up.
Benten is supposed to be the lake's guardian,
so she gets jealous and splits them up.
No! Let's head back, then!
We just got in the boat. Let's head to the statue of Benten.
No!
Get down, idiot!
I'm sorry.
Well, it's hot today, so we
should dry off eventually.
Oh, I left my bag at the boat station,
it has a shirt I bought for you.
Here. Try it on.
You should put it on.
You don't like it?
I'll take it when we get to the house.
You should put it on, for now.
Okay, I'll get changed, then.
Huh? Irie... where'd you go?
Where is he?
Dinner.
Irie!
It's not like we can dine in, soaking wet.
Hey, a hamburger!
Thank you.
It's yummy!
Everything tastes great
when you're hungry.
Nah. I don't think even gourmet French or
Italian can compare with this burger.
I wish time would stop in this moment...
In my life...
I've generally had it pretty easy.
But ever since you gave me
that letter, during senior year,
and we started living together,
every day has been a cycle
of trouble and irritation.
I figure...
You might be some kind of test for me.
And being faced with a challenge
for the first time, I panicked.
I was desperate to get away.
So I'm like... a jinx?
But lately,
I've started to think that
a life with no trouble
isn't as much fun as overcoming
challenges. That's how I feel now.
And I'm... a test?
Yes.
And you have to overcome me?
Right.
So, you wanted to run from me,
but you've changed your mind...
Is this a proposal?!
You read way too deep into that!
I'm just saying, I don't
mind living with you.
So, you don't hate me, then?!
You're annoying, but I don't hate you.
Us having dinner together...
Kinda like a date, huh?
Compared to the time when I sent him that love letter,
and even when we first kissed,
I feel much more intimate with Irie now.
Things have changed.
Winter
You want to move out?
I've had plenty of luxury growing up here,
but I want to try living on my own,
and see what I can do by myself.
It'll help me consider my major and career, too.
But, what about Kotoko?
This has nothing to do with her.
Mama.
I agree with him.
Take a shot at doing it on your own.
Right.
353!
354!
Hey, Aihara.
You've been real low
energy since Irie moved out.
You're like a jellyfish.
So...
You wanna treat me to some steak?
No!
Even if I know where Irie is working?
I'll pay!
So, Irie is working here?
I work part-time job here on the weekends, too.
He got the job through me.
Now, hurry up and pick your order.
Okay!
Are you ready to order?
I'll take the steak meal,
with rice, and coffee.
And your friend?
Uh, I'll have a hamburger...
no, the seafood casserole...
Oh, but the fried oyster looks good...
Make up your mind.
Okay!
Oh, Irie!
Uh, I'll have the fried oyster meal, then,
with bread and black-tea.
Very good then, it'll just be a moment.
Please enjoy your food.
See? And all it cost you was a steak dinner.
Yeah!
I haven't talked to him in a while,
so I'm really happy!
You count that as a talking?
Sudo, do you happen to know where Irie lives?
Nope.
He didn’t even tell his parents about that.
That's in-character, though.
Whew, I am stuffed.
Your coffee, sir.
Matsumoto?! What are you doing here?
Sudo introduced this job to me.
Sudo...!
Thanks for treating me!
Wait, I don't have any cash—!
Miss, what about your black tea?
Can I drink it tomorrow?
I'm afraid we don't
offer that service, idiot.
Are you mad I came by...?
I figured you'd show up eventually.
Just don't let my family know, okay?
Here is your fifth cup of coffee.
If you want to fail at studying,
you could do it at home.
"I wonder how."
Shall I pour you a tenth cup of coffee?
Oh, yes.
I'm not sure Irie is into clingy girls.
And it'd be nice if we could use these tables
for a customer who orders more than coffee.
The manager was getting
on his case, earlier.
Really?
Yes.
Order some food.
Okay...
I haven't had much of
an appetite lately, though.
Should I have them make
something nutritious, then?
Okay, sure.
Coming right up.
Huge!
This is our cafe's original
jumbo-sized steak.
You've got more of an appetite
than I thought. Need any help?
Aren't you still on the clock?
I'm just about done for today.
By the way...
Irie gets out at nine.
You wanna shadow him again?
More stalking, then?
Yep!
Sounds like he and Matsumoto
are going home together, tonight.
What?
Yeah.
Today was exhausting...
Let’s go home and have dinner.
Yeah.
Matsumoto lives here...
What a big house!
Man, he's probably getting
son-in-law treatment.
Why?
Why did Irie go home with Matsumoto...?
It might mean they live together.
When I close my eyes, I can see the
two of them, happy together.
He said he didn't hate me.
But does he actually like Matsumoto?
Irie...
Get a load of those baggy eyes!
Like some kind of monster.
I noticed that Aihara
hasn't come by recently.
Really?
Then again, considering how
often she was here...
It should make work easier, right, Irie?
I think... I actually have to give up on Irie.
Kotoko.
Living together?!
If he didn't leave Matsumoto's
house until really late...
That means...
An adult relationship, right?
Don't!
Jinko, stop it.
Sorry, my imagination ran away with me.
Okay, three more!
There. There you go!
Well done.
Sudo.
Oh, Irie.
It's been a long time.
How about a match?
Where is she?
You mean Aihara?
Haven't seen her recently.
Strange.
Yeah, that's the word for her.
Irie!
We need to have a little chat!
Who were you, again?
Man, for a guy with a 200 IQ,
your memory sucks.
I try not to remember
useless information.
Useless?!
Oh, I remember now.
Jinko and Satomi,
from Kotoko's class.
Whats the matter?
Let's talk over there.
So, what is it?
About Kotoko.
She's a total mess, physically
and mentally lately!
Don't you feel sorry?
We can’t let this go, as her friends.
What do you want from me?
We wanna know your situation.
It sounds like you're living
with Yuko Matsumoto.
Kotoko followed you two, and saw as much.
You moved out just to shack
up with another girl... that's cowardly.
The point is, stop making Kotoko suffer!
You need to make it clear to
her if she needs to give up.
That’s all we wanted to say. Goodbye.
I see.
Hey.
Irie...
It's been a long time.
Haven't seen you in a while.
I guess so.
Well...
I better go.
Kinda distant, aren't you?
Stay with me for a while.
I'm waiting for someone.
Uh...
Are you lonely living by yourself?
No.
I spend most of my time with Matsumoto.
With Matsumoto?
Mr. Naoki!
Ayako.
Huh?
This must be Kotoko.
How do you know me?
I thought so!
You're just like my sister described.
Who's your sister?
I am.
Matsumoto!
What’s going on?
This is my younger sister.
Irie's been tutoring her.
I'm studying for exams.
So she reccomended I study with Mr. Naoki.
Not sure how I feel being used as bait...
Ayako, come on.
Come on, show me around the school.
Let's get going.
See you later.
A misunderstanding...
It was just a misunderstanding!
Irie!
He's still single!
Yes! Yes, yes, yes!
I am so glad!
Alright!
It’s my always been my dream to
help a young girl make chocolate like this!
I'm having fun, too!
Listen up...
Valentine's Day, tomorrow, is going
to mark a turning point in your life!
Right!
You've gotta fight!
Yeah!
Unbelievable...!
But... it's not gonnna stop me!
Welcome.
Here I am!
Table for one.
This way, please.
My stomach hurts.
Maybe I overdid it with the coffee?
Why don't you get out of here?
You don’t look well.
Are you going back?
Yes.
The manager said the girls could go
home early, on account of the weather.
You're wasting your time if you're
waiting to give Irie some Valentine's chocolate.
He's coming over to tutor
my sister tonight, again.
Irie!
Alright. Now's the time.
Kotoko?
Are you OK?
It hurts.
Are you feeling better, miss?
Manager,
I'm sorry for troubling you.
Irie, walk her home.
You're friends, right?
Oh, that's fine, there's no need.
It's fine. Plus, I'd be worried about
you alone out in that weather.
That okay with you, Irie?
Right.
This is some crazy weather...
I don't see anyone on the road.
What should we do?
It's ten minutes to my apartment,
on foot. You wanna come over?
We can call from my house
and have mom come and pick you up.
Let's go.
Stop gawking.
Everything's so tidy.
Has Matsumoto come over before?
No. You're the first guest here.
Wait, aren't you supposed to tutor today?
I cancelled because of the weather.
Hey, it's me, Naoki.
What a wonderful Valentine's Day...!
No! Calm down, and hear me out.
But, this is...
Her stomach hurts.
It's just a fleeting dream
before she comes to pick me up...
You're kidding. Hang on! Wait!
Dammit, she hung up.
What’s wrong?
She doesn't want to drive in this weather.
So I'm supposed to let you stay the
night, and she's gonna pick you up tomorrow.
Hello. This is Puffer House.
Oh, that sounds like Kinnosuke!
And that voice is Irie's mom?
Perfect timing! Could you give
Mr. Aihara a message for me?
Sure.
Kotoko's going to be
spending the night out,
but he doesn't need to worry.
Uh, so where's she staying?
She's spending the night at Naoki’s apartment.
She's what?!
Boss, where does Irie live?
What brought that on?
He didn't even tell his family.
Although...
Although? Although what?!
I seem to remember it being an apartment in Shimokitazawa.
Boss, I'm heading out early!
Hey! Kinnosuke!
The night belongs to two of us.
Just like in a romance novel.
Only one room...
And only one bed.
Hey.
Yes?!
Your turn for the shower.
Th-thank you.
Here.
Use this one.
Th-thanks...
Well, I’ll  take that shower.
Are you nervous?
Not at all!
Why would I be?
Thanks for the shower.
Yeah.
What are you eating?
Pasta.
Aren’t you hungry?
Nah, I'm okay.
My stomach was hurting anyway.
I see.
Where are you going?
To buy some rice. All I
have is frozen pasta.
I'll just have pasta, then.
You collapsed from stomach pain.
I'll make rice porridge, it's good for digestion.
That's okay, I'm not...
I'm heading out.
I wouldn't be able sleep with
your stomach rumbling, anyway.
Stupid!
Dammit all!
Kotoko!
Thank you for the meal!
I’m going to bed.
Here we go...!
Oh, I’ll sleep in the sofa.
Yeah, you will. Use your coat for a blanket.
But... I'm sick.
Your stomach sounded
healthy enough, earlier.
So mean. A sadist. Downright inhuman.
Cold-blooded!
Uh... I feel kinda guilty now.
Yeah, I can see why you would.
Hey. This place isn't haunted, is it?
Of course not.
Are you cold?
Yeah, I am.
Hey...
So annoying... have it your way.
I guess it is just the two of us, all night.
How about a kiss?
Or would you want more...?
Irie...
Well, regardless of what you want,
I'm not trying anything.
Good night.
Oh... good night.
Are you feeling down again?
How could I?
I don't want my mom to dictate my life.
What do you mean?
If anything happened tonight between us,
I'd be falling right into her little plot,
and I'd be dancing to her
tune for the rest of my life.
I think I understand.
That’s part of why I moved out.
So, don’t expect anything.
Just go to sleep.
Okay.
Being in bed with you...
It feels like I'd
miss too much if I slept.
He looks so handsome asleep...!
Good morning. Did you sleep well?
No. I was too focused on you.
Oh, you!
You looked ridiculous in your sleep.
No way!
“Spring”
Chibi's grown a lot, huh?
You're the only one who doesn't grow up, Kotoko.
“The 2nd year on campus”
Irie!
It's been a year since we joined up, huh?
Time flies.
And you're still the ball girl.
You've made no progress.
Irie!
I actually have a message from your mom.
What?
A friend of our dads is getting married,
and they're all going to Kyushu tomorrow.
So, since Yuki and I will
be watching the house,
I'm supposed to call you
if anything happens.
Got it.
Kotoko!
Ayako! Congratulations on making it into Tonan U.
Are you joining the tennis club?
Glad to be aboard!
Now who's this lovely girl
who's exactly my type?
She's the little sister of the
other girl who's exactly your type!
I'm Ayako Matsumoto. It's nice to meet you.
Matsumoto’s sister?
So, you're probably
decent at tennis, right?
Yes!
Let's see what you can do, then.
I'm ready when you are.
Ayako won the inter-high competition before.
Mr. Naoki! Did you see that? What do you think?
Was that impressive or what?
All thanks to your lessons! Thank you, Mr. Naoki!
Why's she all over him?!
When I had Irie start coming over to tutor her
she said she'd become the cupid for our romance...
But, now...
So Ayako is after Irie too?
She says all's fair in love and war.
In other words, she's declared war on us.
Mr. Naoki!
What did you think? Come on, Mr. Naoki!
Your favorite, Yuki, curry with salisbury steak.
Go ahead and eat.
I think it turned out pretty good.
How about it? Is it good?
Yeah.
Really? That's great!
I guess at least my cooking
has improved.
Yes.
Time to eat.
Good.
Yuki, the bath is ready.
Are you asleep, Yuki?
I'm coming in.
What’s wrong, Yuki?
My stomach hurts... it hurts so bad!
Oh, what do I do?!
I know!
Irie...
Hold on. I'll be just a second.
Hang in there, Yuki.
Irie, family call.
Hurry!
Oh, Irie!
Well, Yuki's not feeling well!
I don't know what to do!
Calm down. Tell me
exactly what's going on.
After eating dinner, he said his stomach hurts.
He seems to be in a lot of pain.
When was dinner?
Half past six.
How do you feel?
I’m fine.
Then it’s not food poisoning.
Call an ambulance and go to
straight to Sugimoto Hospital.
The family doctor works there.
Okay.
I'll head there right away.
I'm counting on you, Kotoko.
Right!
We did an ultrasound, and it seems
to be a case of intussusception.
It's a condition where some
of the intestine folds into itself.
Is it serious?
Well, severe cases can be terminal—
Doctor! You have to help him!
Please! Operate on him—
No, no, it's alright! Thankfully,
we caught this early on.
It won't even require surgery.
Really?
Yes.
Irie...
How is he?
The doctor took care of it right away.
He should be fine now.
That's good.
It's like...
I can't do anything,
unless you tell me what to do.
I just get nervous and...
Oh, right, I...
I hadn't called your parents yet.
I’ll do that now.
Kotoko.
I am just...
So stupid.
My wallet, my contact book...
and the the note with the number in Kyushu...
I forgot them all.
I am just such an idiot.
Thank you,
Kotoko.
Irie...
I was scared...
I was so scared!
It’s all right now.
It was the first time he
had treated me so kindly.
His embrace was gentle,
and it made all my tension fade away,
as I cried so much it felt like
my heart and eyes were melting...
Hi, Yuki. Ma'am.
Kotoko, I am so grateful for
what you did! Thank you.
It’s nothing. I only called the ambulance.
But since they caught the condition early,
he's recovering without any trouble.
He should be able to leave in three days.
All thanks to you, Kotoko.
3 days, huh?
Yeah.
I bet you wish I was gonna be here longer,
so you could spend more time with Naoki, huh?
I would never!
Naoki!
How are you feeling, Yuki?
Irie...!
There she goes.
Kotoko's true nature.
Kotoko, since Naoki is here,
why don't the two of
you keep Yuki company?
I'll go take take care of this laundry.
Okay.
Hello.
I like how lively your family is, Yuki.
We've just got one loudmouth.
My name is Nobuhiro. You can call me Non.
I'm Nobuhiro's mother.
I'm Yuki's brother.
And I'm, uh...
His big sister?
Well, not exactly, sort of...
an acting big sister?
It's nice to meet you.
Me too.
What grade are you in, Non?
I would be in fifth grade...
Would be?
He's been hospitalized a lot,
so he has to repeat fourth grade.
He's the same age as Yuki, then.
Yes.
But...
I've fallen behind at school, now...
I can tutor you, then.
Really?
Yes.
Hey, Non.
My brother always gets
the best grades, y'know.
Really?
Awesome...
I'll study hard, then!
Whats wrong?
The kids who are hospitalized...
They're all so little,
but they have to deal with
those big IV needles,
and have to take gross medicine...
They can't even eat the snacks they like.
I feel bad for them.
Your pity doesn't help them, though.
Yeah...
But,
if it was you...
Maybe you could find a cure for diseases that don't have one,
or become a doctor,
and help people heal in a snap.
You seem like you could do anything.
I bet everyone would be happy, then.
Since nothing's impossible for you.
Have a nice day.
Kotoko?
Kin?
Hey, Kotoko!
What're you doing here?
I come to see Yuki.
Do you have a cold or something, Kin?
Yeah...
Chilblains.
Wait, no, no, no,
Frostbite! That's it.
Kinda still hurting some
some frostbite I got...
Frostbite?
Yeah...
Yuki.
Congratulations on getting discharged.
Thanks.
Kotoko.
You have been a huge help.
Thank you so much.
Oh, no, I didn't do much.
Hey.
Still up?
While I was in the hospital...
You looked after me a bunch...
So, thanks.
I guess he's not all bad!
“Summer”
Irie!
Boo!
What are you reading?
Is it something naughty?
You think they stock those in the school library?
Good point.
So, hey...
What now?
Your mom gave me a message.
What is it this time?
Nothing much.
It’s about Chibi.
Chibi?
Kiyosato?
Yeah, the heat seems to be really getting to Chibi.
Well, the breed comes from Switzerland...
He's only just become fully grown, so maybe the heat's too much.
That's why, over the Obon holiday,
she wants to take a family trip
to stay at a friend's guest house.
Are you coming?
Or would you rather just spend time with me?
That's obviously not the case.
Well, I should be able to read in
peace and quiet, so I may as well go.
Really?
Yeah.
That's great!
Oh, Kotoko.
Hey there!
You've got good news, don't you?
So, what happened?
I'm going on vacation with
Irie over summer break!
Only two of you?
No. It’s a family tour.
Of course.
But,
it's still spending a whole week together!
A midsummer romance!
Maybe you two will finally...
Yeah, that's not happening.
Maybe we should go looking
for a romantic summer escapade, too.
Do you want to come with us, then?
Good idea!
Yeah, I like it!
Aihara...
You keep doing basic drills in this heat...
You're a hard worker.
But, I've got a fun summer
vacation coming up!
Going anywhere in particular?
Kiyosato. It's an Irie family vacation.
Oh, really?
And Irie is going, too?
Of course. It's his family!
Thanks for the excellent tip.
My family happens to have
a villa in Kiyosato.
One with a tennis court...
Maybe I should invite Irie to come play.
What a coincidence!
My family also has a villa in Kiyosato.
Tennis in Kiyosato... sounds good!
Let's all get some games in, and have fun!
Right, Matsumoto?
Huh? Where'd she go?
She left.
Here you are.
Since The Puffer House is
closing over summer,
I managed to grab a short-term
live-in job in Kiyosato.
No telling when the so-called
genius might show his true colors.
So I'm worried about Kotoko.
I see. I'd better be careful.
The air's so clean out there!
Here you go!
Thanks.
There they are.
Who are the girls in the fancy car?
They're in our tennis club.
A pair of sisters who are both after Irie.
Oh, so they're you're love rivals, then?
Mr. Naoki, thanks for having us.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Yuko Matsumoto, from the
same department as Naoki.
Hello, there.
I am her sister, Ayako.
Naoki used to be my tutor.
It's not much, but we brought this.
Thank you so much.
Hope you like it.
For me, too?
Yes.
Well, thank you!
Excuse us, please.
I'll take it.
I made doughnuts!
And I baked a cake.
Try it.
My cake...
Stupid dog!
Where'd it even come from?
Hey! Sorry, sorry!
Sudo?
This is my dog, his name's Tsunayoshi.
The leash slipped my
hand while we were walking,
and he ran here, after the aroma!
So, I had to chase after him, and here I am.
Man, is this a coincedence, or what?
Hey, Aihara, could you
help me out and get some water?
Here you are.
I think they bought my coincedence act,
but I actually walked through the mountains to get here.
Yeah, I doubt you'd coincidentally
work up that kind of a sweat.
Hey Boss, I better head off to work.
Yeah. Do a good job out there!
Yessir.
Irie, we should probably get going, too.
I probably should, too.
If you'll excuse us.
See you later.
"Orienteering"
It feels nice out here!
Right, Mr. Naoki?
“The 1st pair Naoki & Ayako with Chibi”
There's the third station!
“The 2nd pair Sudo & Yuko with Clarice”
Come on, Clarice.
Beautiful scenery
nice cool shade,
and the beautiful and cool Matsumoto.
Sudo, we're at the fifth station.
Gotta get the stamp...
Whoa, almost fell...
Ma...Ma...
M-Matsumoto, wait up!
“The 3rd pair Kotoko &
Yuki with Tsunayoshi”
Here's number seven.
Kotoko, get the stamp.
Okay.
Where to next?
This way. Come on.
Right.
Tsunayoshi...
Fried noodles, ice cream and frankfurters!
So good!
Huh? Kin?!
Kin!
If it ain't Satomi and Jinko!
You look right at home.
And the food looks great.
You're working part time here?
Yeah, you got it.
Look, it says "Kinnosuke's
takoyaki" on the menu.
Oh, I wanna try that.
Right?
Sure thing.
Here. On the house. Eat up.
Thanks!
Thanks.
Good stuff, huh?
How is it? Fantastic, right?
Whacha think?
It's really tasty, Kin.
I bet Kotoko would love these.
Guess I'll go deliver an afternoon snack, then!
I think she might not be
there by the time you get there.
Huh? Then where is she?
She went hiking in the woods.
They went in pairs.
Pairs?!
With who?
Irie—
Irie?!
In the woods with
Irie? What the hell!
I was going to say Irie’s brother!
What a goon.
It's awful late...
And it's such a straightforward path.
We're back.
Yep.
Huh? They're still not back from the trail?
The Aihara pair isn't back yet.
Maybe Kinnosuke found them
and they went somewhere.
Kinnosuke?
Yeah, he probably went to find Kotoko.
He ran off from his job.
Hey. Yuki,
Are you sure this is the right way?
We haven't seen any new stations after the seventh one.
We are totally lost.
Kotoko!
Where are you?!
Hey, maybe we should try
and find another path...
In this situation,
we've got a better chance
of surviving if we stay put.
Someone's gonna be looking for us.
Really?
Dammit all!
I bet Irie's all over her...!
Here.
Thanks.
Kotoko?!
Where are you?!
Hey.
Irie!
Naoki!
Irie...!
I knew you'd come and find us!
We're saved!
Chibi led me to you.
Be grateful.
Thank you!
Good boy!
Hey, you found them!
That's a relief.
Sudo!
Sudo...
Could you make sure they get back safely?
There's something I want to see.
Leave it to me.
Let’s go.
Aw, crap...
Dammit!
Can't hold on much longer...
I'm done!
Kotoko—!
Grab on already.
Huh, so how do you adjust it?
Try now.
Okay.
Hey Kin,
you're not gonna go hang out with Kotoko?
Are you too busy?
I owe Irie now.
So, where is it?
I get to go on this lovely trip with Irie...
But there's almost no chances
to be alone with him.
Irie...
All this beautiful nature...
If I could be alone with Irie here,
it'd be so romantic.
Kotoko.
Kotoko!
Irie?
What’s wrong?
There's a pretty river over there.
Care for a walk?
Okay.
Thank you.
Somehow you seem different today.
Come and sit here.
Okay.
Listen..
You always talk about how you like me,
but do you know how I feel?
How you feel?
I'd guess you don't really see me that way.
Idiot.
You're wrong, there.
Another one?!
A dream...
I guess.
But for some reason
I can feel the sensation on my lips.
Naokie Irie: Kanta Sato (EXILE Theater Group)
Kotoko Aihara: Reina Visa
Satomi Ishikawa: Nonoka Yamaguchi (E-girls)
Kinnosuke Ikezawa: Shimon Okura
Jinko Komori: Atsuki Tomori
Sudo: Tetsuya Makita
Producers:  Atsushi Ichikawa  Koji Hyakutake
Director & Script: Minoru Mizoguchi
It was so much fun...
This summer vacation.
Our relationship hasn't really changed,
but...
I was still able to kiss him, in my dreams.